<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="tip0">*Bring the dog!*\n
        If you’re looking for extra workout motivation, bring your dog with you for an outdoor walk or run. Pups need exercise too.</string>
    <string name="tip1">*Can’t sleep? Blame your cell phone.*\n
        Staring at your mobile’s screen at bedtime causes people to take longer to reach the deeper stages of sleep and to spend less time in them.
    </string>
    <string name="tip2">*Graffiti a water bottle.*\n
        To ensure you’re drinking water all day, use a Sharpie to mark up a water bottle with onehour intervals.</string>
    <string name="tip3">*And the 20/20/20 rule.*\n
        If you stare at a computer all day with no breaks, try the 20/20/20 rule, which doctors say reduces eye strain and redness: Take 20 seconds to look at something 20 feet away every 20 minutes.</string>
    <string name="tip4">*Talk it out to build muscle.*\n
        Verbal encouragement can increase the amount of weight you can lift, so pump iron with a supportive friend or work with a trainer.
</string>
    <string name="tip5" >*Eat before you eat.*\n
        If you know you’re going to a party, a buffet, or a big dinner and don’t want to totally bust your diet, eat one to two cups of raw veggies beforehand to give your stomach a bit of a head start.</string>
    <string name="tip6">*Bag and freeze smoothie ingredients before you want the smoothie.*\n
        This way, when you’re craving something sweet, you can toss the ingredients in the blender and drink up—no pre-chopping required.</string>
    <string name="tip7">*Book classes in advance.*\n
        Booking pilates, yoga, spin, or other one-off classes in advance will always force you to go—otherwise, you get charged, since most require a credit card.
</string>
    <string name="tip8">*Smell an orange.*\n
        Several studies have found that the scent of oranges can reduce stress, improve mood, and make you feel way more awake.</string>
    <string name="tip9">*Shop on a full stomach.*\n
        Never go grocery shopping when you’re super-hungry. Why? Because everything looks good, so you’ll undoubtedly start throwing in items you normally might not buy.</string>
    <string name="tip10">*Use your commute to relax.*\n
        Commuting doesn’t have to be stressful: If you take public transportation, download a meditation track or app, close your eyes, and focus on breathing.</string>
    <string name="tip11">*Breakfast person?*\n
        If you’re a breakfast person, eat it within 30 minutes of waking up.Studies show this can do wonders to boost metabolism.</string>
    <string name="tip12">*Always keep a packed gym bag.*\n
        In your car or under your desk at work. That way, when the urge to work out hits, you’ll have no excuses.</string>
    <string name="tip13">*Whiten nails with toothpaste.*\n
        We’ve all heard the one about toothpaste getting rid of zits, but did you know it also can be used to whiten yellowing nails?</string>
    <string name="tip14">*Background do matter!*\n
        Make your phone or computer background a motivational quote.That way, every time you check your phone, you’ll be motivated to get moving.
</string>

</resources>